New York City, 1881
Port Crant Outpost, 1868
...hell are you?
Don't shoot him!
Don't shoot!
We should kill it, Jeooak.
Move away.
Hello.
Don't run.
Don't run away.
Hello.
Don't run.
Alright.
Jump.
Jump Iike you jump before.
Jump, yeah?
Jump.
Jump!
Don't!
Don't shoot him!
Don 't shoot him! Don 't shoot him!
It's alright, Virginia. Be still.
Fighteen have yet to hatch, Jeooak.
Then they are weak ano not Thark.
Leave nothing for the white apes.
Sarkoja!
Let Sola have a hatchling.
Sola can take the Iittle white worm.
Be still.
Be still!
Now we kill it.
Step away, Tal Hajus.
You prize this more highly than my judgement?
Step...
...away.
I claim the right of challenge!
Anö who supports your challenge?
Who will pleöge their metal to mine?
You are blind as a white ape, Tal Hajus.
You will not rule today.
Not today.
See the prize your Jeööak has found!
Is it... a baby white ape?
No!
It is a rare and valuable animal!
It is calleö...
lt is called... Virginia!
Watch. Everyone, step back.
Show them, Virginia.
Jump.
Jump!
By Issus, you will jump tomorrow, Virginia.
Sola, chain him.
Tell Sarkoja to initiate him with the other hatchlings.
I know, I know... Drink... Cool...
The voice of Barsoom.
You can hear it if you choose.